hanwhaprecisionmachinery.com 2019-06-07

# None

hanwhaprecisionmachinery.com operated by Hanwha Group, Hanwha Precision Machinery Co., Ltd, ('Hanwha')

## Your Privacy

Your privacy is of great importance to us. As a user of this web site (the "Site"), you are valued by us and we will take appropriate measures to protect the information provided by and collected from you on the Site in connection with the functions, facilities, products and services offered on our Site (the "Hanwha Services"). As our business changes and grows, so will this policy. Please check back periodically for additions and changes.

## Information We Collect and How we use it

Hanwha Precision Machinery grants you no license or property rights to any such Services and Materials. Hanwha Precision Machinery does not warrant the accuracy, completeness, or reliability of Services and Materials and other items contained on this server or any other server. Therefore, you are not to rely on any Services and Materials provided in this site unless we expressly advise you in writing that you can.

## Cookies

At times, we may use a feature of your browser to send your computer a "cookie". Cookies are used by thousands of web sites in order to enhance your web experience. A cookie is a small data file that assigns a unique anonymous number to your browser from a web server and is stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies can not damage or read information stored on your hard drive. Cookies make your web experience more enjoyable by storing passwords and preferences. You can adjust your browser settings to refuse all cookies or to inform you when a cookie is being placed on your hard drive. However, your election not to accept cookies may diminish your experience with the Site because of additional time needed to repeatedly enter information.

## Disclosure of Personal Information

We will not disclose, sell, trade, or rent Personal Information without your prior consent, except to the extent necessary to provide you with a requested Hanwha Service. In certain rare circumstances, we may be compelled by law to disclose your Personal Information, such as in connection with a lawsuit or other legal proceeding. In the event disclosure is required, we will use reasonable commercial efforts to try to secure confidential treatment of the disclosed Personal Information, including prohibiting use of the information for any commercial purpose.

In addition, we reserve the right to disclose certain information when, in its sole discretion, it determines that such disclosure is necessary to protect Hanwha or its employees, their rights or property, or to protect the physical safety or health of employees of Hanwha or a member of the general public.

Any submissions that you make to any public areas of the Site such as bulletin boards ("Public Areas") will be public and will not be considered Personal Information. We do not control, and are not responsible for, the actions of other users of the Site or of Clients with respect to any information you post in Public Areas. In addition, information that you submit to Public Areas may be collected and used by others to send you unsolicited messages and for other purposes.

## Links to Third Party Sites

You may be able to access third party web sites through links available on this Site. You understand and agree that your use of such third party sites, including other Hanwha sites, will be governed by the privacy policies of those sites and not by this Privacy Statement.

## Children's Personal Information

The Hanwha Services and this Site are not intended for children under the age of 13 years age. We will not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children's Internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Statement by instructing their children to never provide information on this Site without their permission.

## User Access to Personal Information

If you desire access to your own Personal Information, to correct existing Personal Information, or to remove your Personal Information, please contact us using the contact information provided below. If you request removal of Personal Information, you acknowledge that residual Personal Information may continue to reside in Hanwha's records and archives, but Hanwha will not use that information for a commercial purpose. Hanwha reserves the right to maintain your Personal Information if Hanwha has suspended, limited, or terminated your access to the Site for violating the Hanwha Terms of Use.

## Protection of Information

Hanwha will maintain the confidentiality of the information it collects. We maintain internal practices that help protect the security and confidentiality of this information by limiting employee access to and use of this information.

## About Hanwha Group

Each company within the Hanwha Group is an independent legal entity. Hanwha Group is not a legal entity. Hanwha Group is a term to conveniently refer to a group of companies that are tied together by their corporate history. Therefore, please do not mistake the companies by their use of the similar name Hanwha. In particular, no company within the Hanwha Group can accept or receive service of process on behalf of another. No company within the Hanwha Group is legally liable for another unless specifically agreed to in writing to assume such liabilities. This site does not establish any nexus between any of the companies such that you can assume that they can be sued jointly or severally on behalf of another.

This privacy policy was last updated on July 11, 2005.
